<!DOCTYPE ui:UiBinder SYSTEM "http://dl.google.com/gwt/DTD/xhtml.ent">
<ui:UiBinder xmlns:ui="urn:ui:com.google.gwt.uibinder" xmlns:g="urn:import:com.google.gwt.user.client.ui" xmlns:G="urn:import:com.anotherbigidea.flash.movie">
	<ui:with type="org.ednovo.gooru.client.mvp.home.LoginPopUpCBundle"
		field="res" />
	
	<g:HTMLPanel styleName="{res.css.PopupMainLarge}">
		<g:HTMLPanel styleName="{res.css.popupInnerGrey}">    
		<g:HTML>
				<div class="{res.css.popupgreyHeader}">
				    <div class="row">
						<div class="col-md-12 col-xs-12">Copyright Policy</div>
					</div>
					<div class="clearfix"></div>
				</div>					
				<div class="{res.css.popupContentScroll}">
						<div class="{res.css.textContentDiv}">
						    <div class="termsOfUserMessageDiv">
							<span class="{res.css.termsOfUserMessageText}">
								CLIENT COPYRIGHT &amp; INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY POLICY
							</span>
							</div>
						</div>
						<div class="{res.css.termsSubTitle}">Notification of Copyright Infringement:</div>
						<div class="termsContentDiv">
							<span class="{res.css.termsTextLine}">
								Ednovo, Inc., hereafter referred to as EDNOVO (“
								<i>EDNOVO</i>
								”) respects the intellectual property rights of others and expects its users to do the same.
							</span>
							<span class="{res.css.termsTextLine}">It is Ednovo’s policy, in appropriate circumstances and at its discretion, to disable and/or terminate the accounts of users
								who repeatedly infringe or are repeatedly charged with infringing the copyrights or other intellectual property rights of others. User
								accounts that accrue three Qualifying Infringements will be subject to termination. A “Qualifying Infringement” is defined as (i) receipt of a valid infringement 
							    notice that results in the removal of the user’s material or reference or link to material from the Site where no valid counter notice is received or (ii) 
							    removal of a user’s material or reference or link to material from the Site, in the absence of a “take-down” notice, because we obtain actual knowledge that 
							    the material is infringing or we become aware of facts or circumstances from which the infringing nature of the material is apparent.</span>
							<!-- <span class="{res.css.termsTextLine}">Infringements will be subject to termination. A “Qualifying Infringement” is defined as (i) receipt of a valid infringement 
							    notice that results in the removal of the user’s material or reference or link to material from the Site where no valid counter notice is received or (ii) 
							    removal of a user’s material or reference or link to material from the Site, in the absence of a “take-down” notice, because we obtain actual knowledge that 
							    the material is infringing or we become aware of facts or circumstances from which the infringing nature of the material is apparent.</span> -->
							<span class="{res.css.termsTextLine}">
								In accordance with the Digital Millennium Copyright Act of 1998, the text of which may be found on the U.S. Copyright Office website at
								<a href="http://www.copyright.gov/legislation/dmca.pdf" class="privacyLinkText" target="_blank">http://www.copyright.gov/legislation/dmca.pdf</a>, Ednovo will respond expeditiously to claims of copyright infringement committed using the
								Ednovo website or application (the “
								<i>Sites</i>
								”) that are reported to Ednovo’s Designated Copyright Agent, identified in the sample notice below.
							</span>
							<span class="{res.css.termsTextLine}">If you are a copyright owner, or are authorized to act on behalf of one, or authorized to act under any exclusive right under
								copyright, please report alleged copyright infringements taking place on or through the Sites by completing the following DMCA Notice of
								Alleged Infringement and delivering it to Ednovo’s Designated Copyright Agent. Upon receipt of the Notice as described below, Ednovo will take
								whatever action, in its sole discretion, it deems appropriate, including removal of the challenged material from the Sites.</span>
							<h2 align="JUSTIFY">
								<a name="_DV_C19"></a>
								<i>DMCA Notice of Alleged Infringement (“Notice”)</i>
							</h2>

							<span class="{res.css.termsTextLine}">
								<i> 1. Identify the copyrighted work that you claim has been infringed, or - if multiple copyrighted works are covered by this Notice - you
									may provide a representative list of the copyrighted works that you claim have been infringed.</i>
							</span>

							<span class="{res.css.termsTextLine}">
								<i> 2. Identify the material that you claim is infringing (or to be the subject of infringing activity) and that is to be removed or access to
									which is to be disabled, and information reasonably sufficient to permit us to locate the material, including at a minimum, if applicable,
									the URL of the link shown on the Site(s) where such material may be found.</i>
							</span>

							<span class="{res.css.termsTextLine}">
								<i> 3. Provide your mailing address, telephone number, and, if available, email address.</i>
							</span>

							<span class="{res.css.termsTextLine}">
								<i> 4. Include both of the following statements in the body of the Notice:</i>
							</span>
							<ul>
								<li>
									<span class="{res.css.termsTextLine}">
										“
										<i>I hereby state that I have a good faith belief that the disputed use of the copyrighted material is not authorized by the copyright
											owner, its agent, or the law (e.g., as a fair use).”</i>
									</span>

								</li>
								<li>
									<span class="{res.css.termsTextLine}">
										“
										<i>I hereby state that the information in this Notice is accurate and, under penalty of perjury, that I am the owner, or authorized to act
											on behalf of the owner, of the copyright or of an exclusive right under the copyright that is allegedly infringed.”</i>
									</span>

								</li>
							</ul>

							<span class="{res.css.termsTextLine}">
								<a name="_DV_C28"></a>
								<i> 5. Provide your full legal name and your electronic or physical signature.</i>
							</span>

							<span class="{res.css.termsTextLine}">
								<a name="_DV_C29"></a>
								<i> Deliver this Notice, with all items completed, to Ednovo’s Designated Copyright Agent:</i>
							</span>

							<span class="{res.css.termsTextLine}">
								<a name="_DV_C30"></a>
								Copyright Agent
								<br />
								c/o Ednovo
								<br />
								Saket Munshaw
								<br />
								c/o Ednovo
								<br />
								1032 Elwell Court
								<br />
								Palo Alto, CA 94303
								<br />
								dmca@goorulearning.org
								<br />
								(650) 331-0219
								<br />
							</span>

							<span class="{res.css.termsSubTitle}">Notification of Other Intellectual Property (“IP”) Infringement:</span>

							<span class="{res.css.termsTextLine}">If you believe that some other IP right of yours is being infringed by a user, please provide Ednovo’s Designated Copyright
								Agent (specified above) with the following information:</span>

							<span class="{res.css.termsTextLine}">1. Your full legal name and your electronic or physical signature.</span>

							<span class="{res.css.termsTextLine}">2. Information reasonably sufficient to permit Ednovo to contact you or your authorized agent, including a name, mailing
								address, telephone number and, if available, an email address. </span>

							<span class="{res.css.termsTextLine}">
								3. Identification of the IP alleged to have been infringed, including (i) a complete description or explanation of the nature of the IP, (ii)
								evidence that you own the IP in the relevant jurisdiction, including copies of relevant patents, registrations, certifications or other
								documentary evidence of your ownership, and (iii) a showing sufficient for Ednovo to determine without unreasonable effort that the IP has
								been infringed
								<strike>;</strike>
								.
							</span>

							<span class="{res.css.termsTextLine}">4. Information reasonably sufficient to permit Ednovo to identify the use being challenged. </span>

							<span class="{res.css.termsTextLine}">
								5.
								<i>Include both of the following statements in the body of the Notice:</i>
							</span>

							<ul>
								<li>
									<span class="{res.css.termsTextLine}">
										<a name="_DV_C132"></a>
										<a name="_DV_M53"></a>
										<a name="_DV_C134"></a>
										<a name="_DV_M54"></a>
										<a name="_DV_C136"></a>
										<a name="_DV_M55"></a>
										<a name="_DV_C137"></a>
										<a name="_DV_M56"></a>
										<a name="_DV_C139"></a>
										“
										<i>I hereby state</i>
										that
										<i>I</i>
										have not authorized the challenged use, and
										<i>I</i>
										have a good
										<i>
											<strike>-</strike>
										</i>
										faith belief that the challenged use is not authorized by law
										<i>.” </i>
									</span>

								</li>
								<li>
									<span class="{res.css.termsTextLine}">
										<a name="_DV_C141"></a>
										<a name="_DV_M57"></a>
										<a name="_DV_M58"></a>
										<a name="_DV_C144"></a>
										<a name="_DV_M59"></a>
										<a name="_DV_M60"></a>
										<a name="_DV_M61"></a>
										<a name="_DV_M62"></a>
										<a name="_DV_C149"></a>
										<a name="_DV_M63"></a>
										“
										<i>I hereby state</i>
										under penalty of perjury that all of the information in the notification is accurate and that
										<i>I am the owner of</i>
										the IP, or authorized to act on behalf of the owner
										<i>of the IP.”</i>
									</span>

								</li>
							</ul>

							<span class="{res.css.termsTextLine}">
								<a name="_DV_M64"></a>
								Upon receipt of notice as described above, Ednovo will seek to confirm the existence of the IP on the Sites, notify the user who posted the
								content including the IP, and take whatever action, in its sole discretion, it deems appropriate, including temporary or permanent removal of
								the IP from the Sites.
							</span>
						</div>
					</div>
			</g:HTML>
		<g:FlowPanel styleName="{res.css.popupgreyFooter}">
		    <g:HTMLPanel styleName="{res.css.privacyCloseButton}">
		    	<!-- <g:Button ui:field="termsCloseBtn" res.cssName="primary">OK</g:Button>  -->
		    	<g:Button ui:field="termsCloseBtn" styleName="primary">OK</g:Button>   
		    </g:HTMLPanel>
			
		</g:FlowPanel>
		</g:HTMLPanel>
	</g:HTMLPanel>
</ui:UiBinder> 