  <!DOCTYPE ui:UiBinder SYSTEM "http://dl.google.com/gwt/DTD/xhtml.ent">
<ui:UiBinder xmlns:ui="urn:ui:com.google.gwt.uibinder" xmlns:g="urn:import:com.google.gwt.user.client.ui">

	<g:HTMLPanel styleName="PopupMainLarge">
		<g:HTMLPanel styleName="popupInnerGrey">
		<g:HTML>
		    <div class="popupgreyHeader">
				    <div class="row">
						<div class="col-md-12 col-xs-12">Privacy Policy</div>
					</div>
					<div class="clearfix"></div>
				</div>
			<div class="popupContentScroll">
							<div class="policyTextHeade">
								<span>
									<b>Gooru’s Privacy Policy And Data Security Principles</b>
								</span>
							</div>

							<div class="lastUpdated">Effective March 15, 2016</div>
							<div class="textContentDiv">
							<span>
								At Gooru (
								<b>"Gooru", "our" "us"</b>
								or
								<b>"we"</b>
								) we believe that education is a human right.
							</span>
							<span class="policyTextLine">
								Gooru provides teachers and students with access to free, quality digital content and data with the goal to improve their interest and engagement in class. Data is a critical component of our work, powering personalized learning experiences in Gooru for users to visualize and customize their learning. However, we are mindful of user questions and concerns regarding the use and disclosure of their personal information and the tracking, usage and sharing of their data. 
							</span>
							<span class="policyTextLine">
								The following Privacy Policy informs you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personal information that Gooru obtains from visitors to our website, http://www.gooru.org (this "Site") and users of our services. They also provide transparency to students, parents, school districts and teachers as to how data is collected and used. The Privacy Policy (the “Policy,”) as it may be amended, governs access to and use of Gooru’s Site and its Services.  By accessing and using our Site and Services, you consent to the information and data handling practices and policies described in this Policy, as it may be amended.
							</span>


							<span class="policyTextLine">
								<b>Capitalized terms not defined in this Policy have the meanings given to them in our Terms of Use.</b>
							</span>
							<br></br>
							<span class="policyTextLine">
								<div><b>I. Information and Data Collection and Use by Gooru</b></div>
								</span>
								<span class="policyTextLineNew">   
								<div> 
								As a not-for-profit education technology company, our goal is to collect only the information about our users and their use of our Site and Services that will help us provide the best online learning experience possible. Our primary goals in collecting information are to provide and improve our Site, services, features and content, to administer your use thereof (together, the "Gooru Service") and to enable users to enjoy and easily navigate the Site.  The information obtained from users of the Gooru Service include Personally Identifiable Information, and Non-Identifying Information, including Data.
								<br></br></div>
						
								    	<span class="policyTextLine paragraph">
								<b>A. Personally Identifiable Information</b>
									<br></br>
							</span>
									<div class="paragraph">
								<b>What is Personally Identifiable Information?</b> When you register to create an account on the Site we will ask you for Personally Identifiable Information as those terms are defined under the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act of 1974 (codified as 20 U.S.C. § 1232g) (“FERPA”), which includes your name, email address, age, username and password, date of birth, gender and grade level in school. We will only ask about your grade level if you are age 13 or older. Basically, it means any information about you that can be used to contact or identify you. </div>
							</span>

							<span class="policyTextLine paragraph">
								<b>How We Use Your Personally Identifiable Information:</b>
								 We use your Personally Identifiable Information such as date of birth to validate your eligibility to use Gooru. We use your email to contact you with newsletters or other information that may be of interest to you. However, if you identified your role as a student on Gooru, we will not send you newsletters. If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive such communications from us, please follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in any of the communications. (See "Changing or Deleting Information," below.)
								<br></br>
							</span>
							<span class="policyTextLine paragraph">
							    <b>B. Non-Identifying Information </b> 
							    	<br></br><br></br>
								<div ><b>What is Non-Identifying Information?</b> We collect information that you provide or is generated in connection with your use of the Site and the Service (e.g., without limitation, search terms entered, pages viewed, and school network information) ("Non-Identifying Information "). Certain Non-Identifying Information might be considered a part of your Personally Identifiable Information if it were combined with other identifiers (for example, combining your IP address with your school network information) in a way that enables you to be identified. But the same pieces of information are considered Non-Identifying Information when they are taken alone or combined only with other non-identifying information (for example, your viewing preferences). <br></br></div>
								<br></br>
								<div ><b>How We Use Non-Identifying Information:</b>  We may combine your Personally Identifiable Information with Non-Identifying Information and aggregate it with information collected from other Gooru Users (defined below) to provide you with a better experience, to improve the quality and value of the Gooru Service and to analyze and understand how our Site and the Gooru Service are used. We may also share your Non-Identifying Information in the manner described in Section II below.</div>
							</span>

							<span class="policyTextLine paragraph">
								<b>C. Data Collection</b>
									<br></br>
							</span>
							<span class="policyTextLineNew">
								<div class="paragraph">Gooru collects data, including Student Data, regarding each user’s usage and activity within the Gooru Service. The usage data that Gooru collects includes time spent studying the collection or resources, User reactions for each resource, and User’s performance on assessments. “Student Data” means information a student provides or generates through the student’s use of the Gooru Site or Service including, but not limited to, number of views, time spent on a particular collection, student reactions to a resource and student attempts in answering questions in a collection.<br></br></div>
								<br></br>
								<div class="paragraph"><b>How We Use Collected Data: </b>Through the use of Data Analytics, the science of drawing conclusions from raw data, Gooru Service analyzes data to generate reports from which Users can obtain real-time feedback on User activity and subject matter proficiency, as well recommendations that will customize the User experience. The tools Gooru provides to Users allow students and their teachers with whom Student Data is shared to use the data to visualize student progress and personalize their learning.  Data also may be shared in the manner discussed in Section II below.</div>
							</span>
							<span class="policyTextLine paragraph">
								<b>D. Log Data</b>
									<br></br><br></br>
								    <div ><b>What is Log Data? </b>When you visit the Site or use the Service, whether you are a signed-in User of Gooru or are just browsing the Site, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website ("Log Data"). This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type or the webpage you were visiting before you came to our Site, pages of our Site and Service that you visit, the time spent on those pages, information you search for on our Site and Application, access times and dates, and other statistics.</div>
								    	<br></br>
								    <div ><b>How We Use Log Data: </b>We use Log Data to monitor and analyze use of the Site the Gooru Service and for the Site and Service’s technical administration, to increase our Site and Service functionality and user-friendliness, and to better tailor it to our visitors’ needs. We also use this information to verify that visitors to the Site and Service meet the criteria required to process requests. We do not treat Log Data as Personal Information or use it in association with other Personal Information, though we may aggregate, analyze and evaluate such information for the same purposes as stated above regarding other Non-Identifying Information.</div>
							</span>
							<span class="policyTextLine paragraph">
								<b>E. Cookies</b>
									<br></br><br></br>
								<div ><b>What are Cookies? </b>Like many websites, we use "cookies" to collect information. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer’s hard disk for record-keeping purposes. </div>
									<br></br>
								 <div ><b>What do we use Cookies for? </b> We use cookies for two purposes. First, we utilize persistent cookies to save your registration ID and login password for future logins to the Site. Second, we utilize session ID cookies to enable certain features of the Site, to better understand how you interact with the Site and to monitor aggregate usage and web traffic routing on the Site. Unlike persistent cookies, session cookies are deleted from your computer when you log off from the Site and Service and then close your browser. Third parties providing services on Gooru’s behalf may also place or read cookies on your browser.
</div>
							</span>
							
								<span class="policyTextLine paragraph">
								<b>F. How Does Gooru Respond to Do-Not-Track Signals </b>
									<br></br><br></br>
								<div>Many web browsers such as Chrome, Mozilla Firefox and Internet Explorer give users the ability to disable, reject, or turn off cookies and other tracking technologies. You can instruct your browser, by changing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to use all portions of the Site or all functionality of the Gooru Service. </div>

							</span>
							
							<span class="policyTextLine paragraph">
								<b>F. Phishing </b>
									<br></br><br></br>
								<div>Identity theft and the practice currently known as "phishing" are of great concern to Gooru. Safeguarding information to help protect you from identity theft is a top priority. We do not and will not, at any time, request your identification in a non-secure or unsolicited e-mail or telephone communication. For more information about phishing, visit the Federal Trade Commission’s website.</div>

							</span>
							<br></br><br></br>
							<span class="policyTextLine">
								<b>II. Information Sharing and Disclosure</b>
							</span>
							<br></br>
							<span class="policyTextLine paragraph">
								<b>A. Aggregate Information and Non-Identifying Information</b>
								<br></br>
							</span>
							<span class="policyTextLineNew">
								<div class="paragraph">We may share aggregated information that does not include Personally Identifiable Information and we may otherwise disclose Non-Identifying Information and Log Data with third parties for industry analysis, demographic profiling and other purposes. Any aggregated information shared in these contexts will not contain your Personally Identifiable Information. If you access the Gooru Service via a third party service, that third party may have provided us with Personally Identifiable Information about you. In such instances we may share Non-Identifying Information that we collect about you with the third party.
<br></br></div>
							</span>

							<span class="policyTextLine paragraph">
								<b>B. Service Providers </b>
								<br></br>
							</span>
							<span class="policyTextLineNew paragraph">
								<div class="paragraph">We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate the Gooru Service, to host the Gooru Service on our behalf, to perform Site-related services (e.g., without limitation, maintenance services, database management, web analytics and improvement of the Site’s features) or to assist us in analyzing how our Site and the Gooru Service are used. These third parties have access to your Personal Information only to perform these tasks on our behalf.  Gooru will endeavor to ensure all third party service providers are obligated not to disclose or use your Personally Identifiable Information for any other purpose. <br></br></div>
							</span>

							<span class="policyTextLine paragraph">
								<b>C. Business Transfers</b>
								<br></br>
							</span>
							<span class="policyTextLineNew paragraph">
								<div class="paragraph">Gooru may transfer, assign or otherwise share some or all of your Personal Information in connection with a merger, acquisition, or reorganization, in which the new owners intend to operate the Service as a going concern, and will use its reasonable efforts to ensure that the new owner handles Personally Identifying Information with privacy standards no less stringent than employed by Gooru.<br></br></div>
							</span>

							<br></br><br></br>

							<span class="policyTextLine">
								<b>III. Data Sharing by Users</b>
								<br></br>
							</span>
							<span class="policyTextLineNew">
							    <br></br>
								<div>Users own and control their Data in Gooru. All Users can opt-in to share their Data created in Gooru with teachers, parents and other educators in their school. Each User, in his or her sole discretion, decides the usage and disclosure of their Data. For example, students may share their Student Data with their Support Network, i.e, all other Users of Gooru who support the learning of a given student User, including parents, teachers, administrators, educators in their school or school network, and Users of after-school-programs. In the event a User opts-in to share their Data with their Support Network, Gooru enables sharing by providing tools to allow the display of Student Data within the Gooru Service so that the student’s Support Network User(s) will have access to view the information.  All Users can see their own Data and the Data of any of the Users they may be supporting by logging into the Gooru Service using their respective school email addresses. <br></br></div>
							</span>

							<br></br><br></br>

							<span class="policyTextLine">
								<b>IV. Changing or Deleting Your Information and Data</b>
								<br></br>
							</span>
							<span class="policyTextLineNew">
							    <br></br>
								<div>All Gooru users may delete the Personally Identifiable Information the user has provided by contacting us. If you would like us to delete your account in our system, please contact us at support@gooru.org with a request that we delete your Personally Identifiable Information from our database. Gooru also allows its users to delete comments and collections created, upon request. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to honor your request. We may retain an archived copy of your records as required by law or for legitimate business purposes, including the resolution of disputes. Generally, it may take up to six (6) months to delete your Personally Identifiable Data after we receive a request.  Please note that there might be some latency in erasing Data from our servers, including archival or backed-up recovery copies.<br></br></div>
							</span>

							<br></br><br></br>

							<span class="policyTextLine">
								<b>V. International Transfer</b>
								<br></br>
							</span>
							<span class="policyTextLineNew">
							    <br></br>
								<div>Your Personally Identifiable Information may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of the state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where you reside, and where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. If you are located outside the United States and choose to provide Personally Identifiable Information to us, this serves as notice that Gooru transfers your Personally Identifiable Information to the United States and processes it there. Your use of the Gooru Service constitutes your consent to Gooru’s Privacy Policy and your agreement to the transfer of your Personally Identifiable Information to the United States and the application of its privacy laws.<br></br></div>
							</span>

							<br></br><br></br>

							<span class="policyTextLine">
								<b>VI. Links to Other Sites</b>
								<br></br>
							</span>
							<span class="policyTextLineNew">
							    <br></br>
								<div>Our Site and Application contains links to other websites. If you choose to click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s website. The fact that we link to a website is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party, nor is it an endorsement of their privacy or information security policies or practices. We do not exercise control over third party websites. These other websites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, or collect data or solicit personal information from you. Other sites follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the personal information you submit to them. We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of the other websites you visit.
<br></br></div>
							</span>

							<br></br><br></br>

							<span class="policyTextLine">
								<b>VII. Children's Privacy</b>
								<br></br>
							</span>
							<span class="policyTextLine">
								We understand how important privacy is to you, which is why we are committed to creating a safe and secure environment that children of all ages can enjoy when learning. 
							</span>

							<span class="policyTextLine paragraph">
								<b><u>A. How Children's Personal Information is Collected</u></b>
								<br></br>
							</span>
							<span class="policyTextLineNew">
							    <br></br>
								<div class="paragraph">We do not collect information about students unless they attempt to register for an Account. When registering for an Account, the student will be directly asked for his or her date of birth (to determine age). For students under 13 years of age, a parent or guardian’s email address will be requested. We will send an email to the parent or guardian’s email address with instructions about how to register for an Account and to create an Account for students under 13 years of age. If the parent or guardian does not respond, all information collected from the child is deleted. Once the parent or guardian registers, he or she can set up a child Account and create a username, password and, optionally, provide the gender of the child.<br></br></div>
							</span>

							<span class="policyTextLine paragraph">
								<b><u>B. How Personal Information about Children is Used </u></b>
								<br></br>
							</span>
							<span class="policyTextLineNew">
							    <br></br>
								<div class="paragraph">To the extent any Personally Identifiable Information is collected about children, it is used for the internal operations of the website and online services, i.e., to provide the Gooru Service and administer inquiries, and as permitted by law.<br></br></div>
							</span>

							<span class="policyTextLine paragraph">
								<b><u>C. Parental Notification and Consent</u></b>
								<br></br>
							</span>
							<span class="policyTextLineNew">
							    <br></br>
								<div class="paragraph">If a parent or guardian learns that their child is using Gooru without their consent, or a parent or guardian consents to their child’s use of the Gooru Service and later decides to revoke his or her consent, the child’s information and Account can be deleted or deactivated by emailing a request to support@gooru.org.<br></br></div>
							</span>

							<span class="policyTextLine paragraph">
								<b><u>D. Parental/Guardian Review</u></b>
								<br></br>
							</span>
							<span class="policyTextLineNew">
							    <br></br>
								<div class="paragraph">As a parent or guardian, you may review your child’s activity on the Site or in the, Services by logging into the child Account or by sending a written request to Gooru at the physical address below.<br></br></div>
							</span>

							<br></br><br></br>

							<span class="policyTextLine">
								<b>VIII. Ongoing Privacy Compliance Efforts</b>
								<br></br>
							</span>
							<span class="policyTextLine">
								Privacy is a top priority at Gooru. We stay updated with privacy laws and best practices within education. For example, we continually review the U.S. Department of Education’s Privacy Technical Assistance Center (PTAC) which is the “one-stop” resource for education stakeholders to learn about data privacy, confidentiality, and security practices related to student-level longitudinal data systems and other uses of Student Data.
							</span>
								<span class="policyTextLine">
							School districts are authorized to share student data with Gooru through the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA) School Official exception which enables school districts to share education records with a third party provider when performing a service or function for the District which it would otherwise use its own employees. For more information on student privacy and FERPA, please visit Privacy Technical Assistance Center at ptac.ed.gov. 
							</span>
							<span class="policyTextLine">
							To the extent student data containing Personally Identifiable Information is provided or created by an employee or agent of a school, school district, local education agency, or county office of education, Gooru will comply with any request by the school, school district, local education agency, or county office of education, to delete the student data, to the extent required by applicable law. 
							</span>
							<br></br><br></br>

							<span class="policyTextLine">
								<b>IX. Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement </b>
								<br></br>
							</span>
							<span class="policyTextLine">
							Gooru cooperates with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. Notwithstanding Gooru’s Privacy Policy and commitment to its data security principles, Gooru reserves the right to disclose any information about you, including your Personally Identifiable Information, to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (including but not limited to subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of Gooru, other users, or third parties, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop activity we consider to be, or to pose a risk of being, illegal, unethical or legally actionable, including without limitation violation of US Copyright Laws.  In some instances, Gooru may share your Personally Identifiable Information in response to legal or judicial process, including warrants and subpoenas that Gooru in good faith believes to be validly issued and enforceable, without prior notice to you.  
							</span>
								<br></br>
								
							<span class="policyTextLine">
								<b>X. Security Measures</b>
								<br></br>
							</span>
							<span class="policyTextLine">
							Gooru values your Personally Identifiable Information and Data, and protects it on the Gooru Service against loss, misuse or alteration by developing and implementing security measures, that include internal  policies, processes and technological solutions.  
							</span>
								
							<span class="policyTextLine paragraph">
								<b>A. Technology Solutions:</b> Gooru uses Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption, a standard security technology to establish an encrypted link between our servers and our Users. SSL allows Users to securely transmit sensitive information like login credentials. Further, User Data is encrypted while stored in Gooru. Data is also replicated, to ensure that in the event of hardware failures, data can be restored. We update these measures as new technology becomes available.
								<br></br>
							</span>
								<span class="policyTextLine paragraph">
								<b>B. Processes:</b> Gooru requires password protected access as the first layer of security.  It is important that Users select strong passwords, and not share their password with others. In the event your password is lost or forgotten, we use identification verification procedures to ensure that you and only you have renewed access to your account.
								<br></br>
							</span>
							<span class="policyTextLine paragraph">
								<b>C. Policies:</b> Gooru restricts the access of employees to its data servers. Access authorization is tracked, and regulated to ensure only currently authorized personnel can access its servers. Those authorized to access the servers are trained on security measures and to identify breaches of security or vulnerabilities in Gooru’s security measures. Training is refreshed every year.
								<br></br>
							</span>
							<span class="policyTextLine paragraph">
								<b>D. In The Event of Breach:</b> No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personally Identifiable Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. We will make any legally required disclosures of any breach of the security, confidentiality, or integrity of your unencrypted electronically stored "personal data" (as defined in applicable state statutes on security breach notification) to you via email or conspicuous posting on this Site in the most expedient time possible and without unreasonable delay, insofar as consistent with (i) the legitimate needs of law enforcement, or (ii) any measures necessary to determine the scope of the breach and restore the reasonable integrity of the data system.
								<br></br>
							</span>
							<span class="policyTextLine paragraph">
								Although Gooru provides appropriate firewalls, procedures and protections, Gooru cannot warrant the security of any Personally Identifiable Information transmitted as our systems are not hack proof.  Data pilferage due to unauthorized hacking, virus attacks, and technical issues is possible and we assume no liability or responsibility for data breaches or loss as a result of such actions.
								<br></br>
							</span>
							<span class="policyTextLine">
								<b>XI. Changes to these Policies</b>
								<br></br>
							</span>
							
							<span class="policyTextLine">
							Gooru’s Policies may be updated from time to time. We will notify you of any material changes by posting the new Policies on the Gooru Service, and providing you notice of the update. Your use of the Gooru Service subsequent to the provision of notice of any changes to the Policies shall constitute your agreement that your use of the Gooru Service is subject to the terms of the revised Policy.  
							</span>
							
							<span class="policyTextLine">
								<b>XII. Contacting Us</b>
								<br></br>
							</span>
								<br></br>
							<span class="policyTextLine">
								If you have any questions about the Gooru Privacy Policy or Data Security Principles, please contact us at:
							</span>

							<span class="contactUs">Gooru</span>

							<span class="contactUs">350 Twin Dolphin Drive, Suite 115</span>

							<span class="contactUs">Redwood City, CA 94065</span>

							<span class="contactUs">650-331-0219</span>

							<span class="contactUs">
							    <a href="mailto:legal@gooru.org">legal@gooru.org</a>
							</span>
					</div>

					</div>

		</g:HTML>
		<g:FlowPanel styleName="popupgreyFooter">
		     <g:HTMLPanel styleName="privacyCloseButton">
					<g:Button styleName="primary" ui:field="privacyCloseBtn">OK</g:Button>
		    </g:HTMLPanel>

		</g:FlowPanel>

	</g:HTMLPanel>
	</g:HTMLPanel>

</ui:UiBinder>